<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hosea 143</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://www.hosea143.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.hosea143.comhttp://www.hosea143.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Liz instagr.am</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;.ig-b- { display: inline-block; }
.ig-b- img { visibility: hidden; }
.ig-b-:hover { background-position: 0 -60px; } .ig-b-:active { background-position: 0 -120px; }
.ig-b-48 { width: 48px; height: 48px; background: url(//badges.instagram.com/static/images/ig-badge-sprite-48.png) no-repeat 0 0; }
@media only screen and (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 2), only screen and (min--moz-device-pixel-ratio: 2), only screen and (-o-min-device-pixel-ratio: 2 / 1), only screen and (min-device-pixel-ratio: 2), only screen and (min-resolution: 192dpi), only screen and (min-resolution: 2dppx) {
.ig-b-48 { background-image: url(//badges.instagram.com/static/images/ig-badge-sprite-48@2x.png); background-size: 60px 178px; } }&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://instagram.com/vimiew?ref=badge&quot; class=&quot;ig-b- ig-b-48&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;//badges.instagram.com/static/images/ig-badge-48.png&quot; alt=&quot;Instagram&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.hosea143.com/socialnetwork/2014/10/22/instagram/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.hosea143.com/socialnetwork/2014/10/22/instagram/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Approved!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This was a day that Zech and I have been working towards for what seems like forever, but in reality it has been only a few months. For so long this day seemed like it was always so far away and seemed as though there was always going to be more time to fill out that mound of paperwork. However… in just a blink of an eye it WAS HERE, it was the day we HAD to have that mound of paperwork finished, our house cleaned, septic tank inspected, background checks done, medical reports ready, firearms locked up, pets vaccinated, and a plethora of other documents ready to hand over to our caseworker. IT WAS HERE. I stayed up late the night before finishing up paperwork and was painting a baseboard just minutes before our caseworker arrived, I know… I have lost my mind! Did I mentioned we completed almost an entire kitchen remodel the week before our home study?!?!  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After long hours, days, weeks, and months of preparation it was finally time. Just saying the words “home study” sent me into a downward spiral of anxiety, so the fact that it was here was terrifying. But, much to my surprise our caseworker was wonderful and she broke the ice before she even stepped foot in our house. She was fun and outgoing; she made us feel so incredibly comfortable through the entire process. We spent the first few hours just talking, laughing, and learning about each other, and the last part was focused on our home. We felt so good after she left and basically crashed, well actually we rushed to a show that They Came Running had scheduled that night. Overall the experience was very stressful and full of anxiety over the unknown, but looking back it was an amazing experience that we absolutely cherish.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what does this even mean, and what is next?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, our home study is the document that tells agencies that we are approved to adopt, which is HUGE! From here we still have lots of paperwork to fill out and turn in, but honestly anything could happen from here on out. We are working with Faithful Adoption Consultants (who we love by the way) and still have plenty of agency applications to fill out and have our profile books assembled and printed. We also have a great deal of fundraising to do before we are fully funded for our adoption. We are in the middle of our first fundraiser effort, which is selling shirts that we designed. So far we have sold over 200 shirts, which is AMAZING! We plan on selling the shirts until people are done buying them ☺  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want to thank all of you who have played a special role in this journey so far! We really love you guys. So, thank you Thank you Thank you from the very bottom of our hearts and we so look forward to continuing this journey with all of you by our sides.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Much Love, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zech and Liz&lt;br /&gt;
Hosea 14:3
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/approved.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Approved!&quot; title=&quot;Approved&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.hosea143.com/2014/07/12/approved/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.hosea143.com/2014/07/12/approved/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We Are Adopting!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are so excited to officially announce that we are adopting! Adoption has been on both our hearts long before we met each other 7 years ago, and we are thrilled that God has opened the doors for us to pursue what He put on our hearts so long ago. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The saying goes “it takes a village” and we completely agree! We are currently in the process of finishing our home study, which is a crucial piece to being adoption ready. We know God has called us to this journey and we have no doubt that He will provide the funds to bring our baby home! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal we are setting is to cover the cost of the first leg of our adoption, and we would be so incredibly grateful for your support whether it’s financially, through prayer, or just by spreading our story. We truly appreciate YOU for taking the time to read a small portion of our story, you really are amazing!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.hosea143.com/2014/07/01/we-are-adopting/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.hosea143.com/2014/07/01/we-are-adopting/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
